COREY CROSBY

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER/DESIGNER

CONTACT

647-996-8674 corey.c.crosby@gmail.com www.coreycrosby.ca github.com/coreycrosby linkedin.com/in/corey-crosby-8aa5b0188/

ABOUT ME

An ambitious sports enthusiast and new graduate from Business Technology Management interested in exploring design, digital marketing, front end development and content creation. Inspired by visual aesthetics and driven to create intuitive design along with 5 years of customer service experience within the retail industry. A determined leader who is dedicated to continuously learn and develop professionally.

EDUCATION

Full-stack Web Development Immersive, General Assembly | 2019

Ryerson University, Bachelor of Commerce -Business Technology Management | 2014-2019

SOFTWARE

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT

HIMI

CSS

lavascrint

React is

Responsive Web Design

GRAPHICS & EDITING

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe Premiere Pro Audacity

DATABASES

Microsoft SQL Server Postgres SQL

VERSION CONTROL

Git

Github

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Fridgenerate

General Assembly - Toronto, ON | April - July 2019

Built fluency in full-stack web development through completing a full-time web development immersive program that included over 500 hours of professional training in 12 weeks. Developed a portfolio of individually and collaboratively focused group projects, including:

• Fridgenerate - A team project built during the Web Development Immersive program at General Assembly – Fridgenerate is a web application used to generate recipes based on ingredients that have been inputted by a user. This full stack application was built with React front end which makes API requests to the Django built back end.

Holy Grails

Ryerson University - Toronto, ON | May 2019

A multimedia development team project built during my Multimedia in Business course at Ryerson University– this website was built using Wix and was used to showcase our ability to create multimedia production such as graphics, audio, text and a logo. Holy Grails is a website created as a cultural hub for sneaker enthusiasts with a heavy emphasis on design and usability.

Business Analysis - Capstone Project

Ryerson University - Toronto, ON | May 2019

The project provided technology solutions to a local restaurant looking to automate restaurant operations.

- Identified, analyzed, and enhanced our client's current business process by gathering requirements from restaurant owners
- Analyzed pizza ordering process by looking at business process design, industry analysis, process redesign, feasibility analysis, risk assessment
- Reached out to top Vendors of a POS system and determined which vendor was best fit through RFP process
- Recommended POS system as a solution to automate restaurant operations and created implementation plan

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sales Associate/Stock Clerk

Browns Shoes - Markham/Richmond Hill, ON | November 2015 - Present

- Assist an average of 40 customers per day in deciding purchases, sizes, shoe types of all departments
- Consistently exceeds sales quota by presenting and offering additional items which resulted in a 35% improvement in sales
- Stock, replenish, and organize inventory with accuracy and efficiency, completing tasks 20% faster than associates
- Received, opened, unpacked, and issued floor merchandise
- Prepared merchandise for shipment

Coach/Youth Mentor

Gary Durrant Basketball Camp - Toronto/London, ON | July 2014 - July 2017

- Involvement in Gary Durrant's basketball camps starting at age 5 progressed to coaching and leadership roles
- Coached and mentored kids 12 and under with basketball and life skills
- Organized equipment/games/drills to improve skills of campers